admarvel.com 2012-12-07

# AdMarvel Privacy Policy

                            AdMarvel Privacy Policy
Effective: 15 October 2010                       Last Updated: December 5, 2011
AdMarvel Inc. ("AdMarvel" or "we", "us", "our") is a technology company that
simplifies the delivery of mobile advertising. This privacy statement ("the Policy")
explains how information is collected and used by AdMarvel and applies to both:
1- the AdMarvel website at www.admarvel.com, (the "Site") and, 2-AdMarvel's
mobile advertising technology services (“Technology”). AdMarvel strives to
collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the
laws of the countries in which it does business. To this end this Privacy Policy
serves as our Safe Harbor Privacy Policy and sets forth the privacy principles
that AdMarvel follows with respect to the transfer of personal information from the
European Union (EU) and Switzerland to the United States. If you have any
concerns about this policy, your privacy when using our Site or our technical
services, please send an email to privacy@admarvel.com and we will try to
address it.
SCOPE
This Policy applies to all personal information received by AdMarvel in the United
States from the EU, Switzerland and all other geographies in any format
including electronic, paper or verbal.
SAFE HARBOR
The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission
have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked
questions (the "Safe Harbor Principles") to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the
EU law requirement that personal information transferred from the EU to the
United States be adequately protected. Consistent with our pledge to protect
personal privacy, AdMarvel adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles.
AdMarvel, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-
Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce
regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from
European Union member countries and Switzerland. AdMarvel has certified that
it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward
transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about
the Safe Harbor program, and to view AdMarvel’s certification, please visit
http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/
AdMarvel, Inc. participates in the EU and Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Framework
as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. As part of our
participation in the safe harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for
disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. If
you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you
should first contact us (as provided above). If contacting us does not resolve your
complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by Internet here, fax to
                                                                                   1

415-520-3420, or mail to Watchdog Complaints, TRUSTe, 55 2nd Street, 2nd
Floor, San Francisco, CA, USA 94105. If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to
lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of
company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether
you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For
information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution
process, click here or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the
addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be
conducted in English.
DEFINITIONS
The following definitions apply throughout this Policy:
    • "AdMarvel" means AdMarvel Inc., its successors, subsidiaries, divisions
       and groups.
    • "Personal information" When AdMarvel uses the term personal information
       in this policy, AdMarvel is referring to information that specifically identifies
       an individual (such as an individual's name, address, telephone number or
       e-mail address), and information about that individual or such individual’s
       activities or preferences when such information is directly linked to
       personal information. Personal information does not include aggregate
       information, which is data we collect about the characteristics and
       activities of users of this Site and AdMarvel's other services or the
       services of our customers, from which any personal information has been
       removed. This privacy policy in no way limits or restricts our collection of
       aggregate information or of non-personal information.
    • "Sensitive personal information" means personal information that reveals
       race, ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or
       trade union membership, or that concerns the individuals health or sex life.
       AdMarvel does not collect “sensitive personal information”.
PRIVACY PRINCIPLES
The privacy principles in this Policy are based on the Safe Harbor Principles.
    •  NOTICE: When AdMarvel collects personal information directly from
       individuals, it will inform them about the purposes for which it collects and
       uses their personal information, the types of non-agent third parties, if any,
       to which AdMarvel discloses that information, and the choices and means,
       if any, that we offer individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their
       personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous
       language when individuals are first asked to provide personal information,
       or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before AdMarvel
       uses the information for a purpose other than that for which it was
       originally collected. If AdMarvel receives personal information from its
       subsidiaries, affiliates or other entities, it will use such information in
       accordance with the notices such entities provided and the choices made
       by the individuals to whom such personal information relates.
                                                                                       2

   •  CHOICE: AdMarvel will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-
      out) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-
      agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose
      for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the
      individual.
   •  DATA INTEGRITY: AdMarvel will use personal information only in ways
      that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or
      subsequently authorized by the individual. AdMarvel will take reasonable
      steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use,
      accurate, complete, and current.
   •  TRANSFERS TO AGENTS: AdMarvel will obtain assurances from its
      agents that they will safeguard personal information consistently with this
      Policy. If AdMarvel has knowledge that an agent is using or disclosing
      personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, AdMarvel will
      take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure.
   •  ACCESS AND CORRECTION: Upon request, AdMarvel will grant
      individuals reasonable access to personal information that it holds about
      them, and AdMarvel will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to
      correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be
      inaccurate or incomplete.
   •  SECURITY: AdMarvel will take reasonable precautions to protect personal
      information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access,
      disclosure, alteration and destruction.
   •  ENFORCEMENT: AdMarvel will conduct compliance audits of its relevant
      privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee that
      AdMarvel determines is in violation of this policy will be subject to
      disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.
      Dispute Resolution - Any questions or concerns regarding the use or
      disclosure of personal information should be directed to the AdMarvel
      Privacy Office at the address given below. AdMarvel will investigate and
      attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure
      of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this
      Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between AdMarvel and the
      complainant, AdMarvel has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution
      procedures of a neutral third party True Ultimate Standards Everywhere,
      Inc. (a Delaware corporation) (“TRUSTe”) (www.truste.com).
WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY
The primary purpose of our Web Site (www.admarvel.com) is to offer information
about AdMarvel and to enable our advertising and publisher partners (collectively,
our "Partners") to use our Technology.
   •  What Information do you Collect on the Web Site and How is it Used?
      We collect Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information")
      from the Web Site. Personal Information includes, for example, your
                                                                                  3

  name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; home and/or
  business telephone, wireless and/or fax number; and/or other information
  that may enable us to contact or identify you as an individual. For example,
  you may choose to send us Personal Information about yourself in an
  email or by completing an online form on this Web Site. We use this
  information only to contact you to respond to your inquiry. Once collected,
  we will store your Personal Information for a reasonable time for record
  keeping purposes. The information that we store is usually deleted as
  space requires or in the normal course of business. You may also choose
  to send us Personal Information if you apply to be an AdMarvel Business
  Partner. We use this information to process your application and to
  administer your Partner account. We may combine the information that
  you submit on our Site with information about you that we receive from
  other online and offline sources in order to provide you with a better
  experience and to improve the overall quality of AdMarvel's services.
  We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII") from
  visitors to this Web Site. The Non-PII may include, without limitation,
  information such as a Web user's IP address, Web pages viewed by a
  Web user, date and time, domain type and the Web user's computer's
  operating system (e.g., Windows XP). We use this information for internal
  system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to
  administer the Web Site. Such information may also be used to gather
  demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service
  Provider from visitors to this Web Site. We automatically receive and
  store certain other types of information whenever you interact with us. For
  example, our servers track the type of Web browser you are using, where
  you travel within the Site, and the page to which you link from the Site.
  This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often customers
  use parts of the Site, so we can make the Site appealing to as many
  customers as possible.
  AdMarvel may share your personal information in connection with any
  merger, sale of AdMarvel assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a
  portion of our business to another company. Aggregate Information:
  AdMarvel may share aggregate information about you and/or your
  customers with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and
  other third parties.
• Other ways we collect information
  Cookies -We may use "cookies" in connection with this Web Site. Cookies
  are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from
  a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies
  to help us manage this Web Site, to customize the Web Site to your
  interests, and to help manage your log in preferences. Most Web
  browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you
                                                                              4

         and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However,
         refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using the Web
         Site, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Web Site or
         certain areas or features of the Web Site. The cookies from our Site do not
         collect personal information, however, we may combine information
         collected through certain cookies we issue on our Site with other personal
         information that you provide to us on the Site.
         Clear GIFs - We may use "clear GIFs" (aka "Web beacons" or "pixel tags")
         and/or similar technologies, in the Web Site and/or in our communications
         with you to enable us to evaluate how visitors are navigating through the
         Web Site. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although
         it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or
         other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the
         Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a
         Web page or message.
    •    Third Party "Linked-To" Web Sites - When you are on the Web Site you
         may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by
         AdMarvel, including other Web sites operated by unaffiliated third parties.
         These sites may collect Personal Information about you. AdMarvel does
         not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible
         for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not
         address the information practices of those other Web sites.
    •    Accessing, Updating and Deleting Your Information - If you would like us
         to update, correct, delete, or deactivate any Personal Information that you
         provided to us on the Web Site, please send your request to
         privacy@admarvel.com. After receipt we will process your request within a
         reasonable period of time. If you are a Business Partner, you may review
         and edit the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on
         the Web Site (e.g., address, telephone number and other contact details)
         by visiting the "My Profile" area of your account or by e-mailing
         admin@admarvel.com. After receipt of your request to review your
         Personal Information we will send you a copy of the Personal Information
         we have on file in your user account (if any). You may send us new or
         updated information at any time. We will respond to your request to
         access, update or delete your information as soon as practicable. Before
         we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies
         or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity
         and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.
TECHNOLOGY PRIVACY POLICY
AdMarvel provides an advertising platform and advertising mediation service to
interconnect mobile publishers with multiple ad sources. Our Technology
facilitates the efficient serving of advertisements within mobile messages (e.g.
SMS) the mobile web and within mobile applications by collecting information
                                                                                       5

associated with these services that you visit or use and the advertisements that
you see associated with such services. You may encounter our technology when
AdMarvel or one of our Business Partners places advertisements on a mobile
web site or application that you visit or use. We use the information collected by
our technology in order to help us efficiently deliver those ads, and for reporting
purposes (e.g., to tell our partners how many ads we delivered in a day.)
   •   Ways we collect information
       AdMarvel does not collect personal information directly from individuals
       but rather receives information via partners’ mobile messages, mobile web
       sites and mobile applications as well as from third party service providers
       (e.g., mobile carrier operators). In this light, AdMarvel relies on our
       customer partners and these third party service providers to inform their
       users about the purposes for which it collects and uses their personal
       information. To the best of our ability we inform our partners the need to
       offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal
       information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be
       used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally
       collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Consistent with the
       U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will
       never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone
       under the age of thirteen (13) without requiring parental consent. When
       AdMarvel receives personal information from the entities described above
       (in the EU, Switzerland or elsewhere), we will use such information only in
       accordance with the principles set forth here, the notices such entities
       provided and the choices made by the individuals to whom such personal
       information relates.
       When our customer partner’s end users connect to the technical service
       on their mobile device, AdMarvel may automatically receive from their
       mobile phone service provider or our customer partner information
       identifying the user’s unique mobile device, their phone number and/or
       other unique identifiers for their device (“Mobile Device Information”). For
       the avoidance of doubt, end users are not “Users” covered by this Privacy
       Policy, and any private information that we collect from the end users is
       governed by the customer partner or mobile phone service provider
       privacy policies, if any, and not this Privacy Policy.
       AdMarvel does use a “pixel tags" and/or similar technologies, in our
       communications to enable us to evaluate when and if advertisements are
       viewable on the mobile device. A pixel tag is typically a one-pixel,
       transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located
       within the advertising creative, which is retrieved from a remote site on the
       Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a
       Web page or message.
                                                                                     6

  • What information is collected by our Technology and how is it used?
    While AdMarvel does not store or maintain personal Information via our
    technology, our technology does collect and use Non-PII, including:
    location and service provider information garnered via the IP address used
    to access the mobile Internet or other means, device identifiers, the type
    of phone or other mobile device used (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry 8800 etc.),
    the date and time of a user’s mobile internet session, whether one of the
    mobile ads we facilitate was delivered and, if applicable, a record if that ad
    was “clicked.”
    AdMarvel on occasion receives personal information for processing but
    does not retain that information in an identifiable form. Specifically,
    AdMarvel, may receive users’ telephone numbers if the mobile operator
    facilitates the delivery of that number to our partner customer. In those
    cases AdMarvel will transmit the number through to the partner customer
    on the behalf of the mobile carrier operator. In a similar manner AdMarvel
    may receive IP addresses of users but does not retain the full set of IP
    address octets after processing.
    AdMarvel uses the collected information to analyze usage trends and
    patterns that will enable the efficient delivery of optimized advertising
    placements on behalf of our business partners. Our technology also uses
    the information to provide reports and measurement analytics to our
    business partners. We may also aggregate this performance information
    and share it with AdMarvel's affiliates, advertisers, customers and
    Business Partners.
GENERAL INFORMATION ABOUT ADMARVEL'S PRIVACY PRACTICES
  • Disclosure of information to third parties
    Service Providers - We may use third party partners to help us manage
    the Web Site and our Technology, and may share usage information with
    those third party partners. (e.g., Web Site or database hosting companies,
    e-mail service providers, and Web Site analytics companies). We disclose
    only that information which is reasonably necessary for our partners to
    perform the tasks we have assigned, and we require our partners to
    adhere to this privacy policy.
    Aggregate Statistics - We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding
    usage as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Web Site and our
    services in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or reports
    that do not describe or identify any individual user.
    Compelled Disclosure - We may disclose any information we have to
    government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so
                                                                                 7

  by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law,
  including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We
  also may disclose user information in connection with investigations or
  when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or
  interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web Site,
  mobile Application or mobile messaging service or anyone else that could
  be harmed by such activities.
• Business Transfer- If AdMarvel should ever file for bankruptcy or have its
  assets sold to, merged with another entity or substantially all of its assets
  are, acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition,
  merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, information
  AdMarvel received from this site or from services provided to our
  customers is an AdMarvel asset and may be transferred to any such entity.
• Consent to Worldwide Transfer and Processing of Personal Information -
  Personal Information given to AdMarvel may be processed by AdMarvel in
  all countries in which AdMarvel operates or in which its affiliates and
  partners operate. Each of these countries has different privacy laws that
  afford varying levels of protection for your Personal Information.
  Regardless of the laws in place in these countries, AdMarvel will treat the
  privacy of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By
  providing your Personal Information to AdMarvel, you consent to AdMarvel
  transmission to, and processing of your information in, any jurisdiction, in
  accordance with this Privacy Policy.
• Information Relating to Children - We do not knowingly collect Personal
  Information from anyone under the age of 18. If we are made aware that
  we have received Personal Information from someone under 18, we will
  use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.
• Security - The security of your information is important to us. We have
  implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in
  our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, due
  to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications
  means, we cannot guarantee that your information, during transmission
  through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care,
  will be absolutely secure from intrusion by others, such as hackers. If you
  contact us by e-mail, a "contact us" or a similar feature on our Web site,
  you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure and that
  a third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.
  Passwords used on our Wed site are encrypted and AdMarvel policies
  preclude access to passwords by anyone at AdMarvel except on a need-
  to-know basis.
  If you create a username and password, you are responsible for
  maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you
                                                                                8

        shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Web Site by you or
        any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or
        use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such
        person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately
        notify AdMarvel of any unauthorized use of your password or account or
        any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit and log out/off
        from your account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility
        to protect your password, control access to and use of your account, and
        notify AdMarvel when you desire to cancel your account on this Web Site.
        We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from
        your failure to comply with this provision. We will have no liability for
        disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third
        parties during or after transmission.
        You have access to your personal information and you may update,
        correct, or delete your member information and email preferences at any
        time by logging-in to your account and changing the information on file or
        by e-mailing AdMarvel at adsupport@AdMarvel.com with your request. To
        protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your
        identity before granting Users profile access.
        YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF
        YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL
        TIMES.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Questions or comments regarding this Policy should be submitted to the
AdMarvel Privacy Office by mail or e- mail as follows:
        AdMarvel Privacy Office
        1875 South Grant St.
        Suite 750
        San Mateo CA 94402
        Email: privacy@admarvel.com
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements
of the Safe Harbor Principles and other privacy requirements. When we do, we
will also revise the “Last Updated” section above. We encourage you to
periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are
protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of this Site
constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
                                                                                    9
